Guide to the Health Systems Management Group, School of Organization and Management, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Health Systems Management Group, School of Organization and Management, Yale University, records
1965-1979
RU 757
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
27
(27 boxes)
The records consist of proposals, reports, correspondence, minutes, pictorial data, videotapes, audiotapes, and notes documenting the activities of the Health Systems Management Group of the Yale School of Organization and Management.
Yale University. School of Organization and Management. Health Systems Management Group
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 30-E (YRG 30-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Management.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of proposals, reports, correspondence, minutes, pictorial data, videotapes, audiotapes, and notes documenting the activities of the Health Systems Management Group of the Yale School of Organization and Management.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Universities and colleges -- Administration; Audiotapes; Videotapes; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. School of Organization and Management. Health Systems Management Group
- Records, 1974-1987; Accession 1989-A-105
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022.
  - Health Maintainance Organization (HMO/MIS)
    - Brief History Jan '81 - Oct '82 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Proposal Material (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Proposal (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dissemination Proposal (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Accounting (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CSMC/PHP Information System Description Draft 1/6/82 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Information System Specifications (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Systems Analysis (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Systems Design (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Data Dictionary (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Information Requirements Analysis (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Telephone Survey: Report and Findings (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Final Report (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Long Term Care
    - Proposal, Grant Material (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Grant Literature (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Grant Application: Resource Utilization Groups, Validation and Refinement of a Case Mix System for Long Term Care Reimbursement (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Proposal, Related Material (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Proposal (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Original Proposal (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - General Literature (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Budget (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Manual for Completion of Form (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Project Notes (I) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Project Notes (II) (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Project Notes (III) (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Notes, Minutes (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Minutes, Data (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/5/84 - 9/14/84 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/21/84 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/26/84 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/28/84 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/3/84 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Notes 10/5/84 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/8/84 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/24/84 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/31/84 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Notes, Minutes 11/7/84 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Notes, Minutes 11/19/84 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Notes, Minutes 12/5/84 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Notes, Minutes 12/13/84 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Notes 1/7/85 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Notes, Charts 1/11/85 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/11/85 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/18/85 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/18/85 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/24/85 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/25/85 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Notes, Minutes 1/29/85 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Notes, Minutes 2/6/85 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Notes, Minutes 2/14/85, 2/15/85, 2/19/85 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Notes of a Meeting with Judy Powell, Chris, Karen, 2/21/1985 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Notes: Nurse Panel 2/22/85 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Notes: Nurse Panel - Weighting of Independent Variables, 2/22/1985 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Notes: Nurse Panel - Time Estimates 2/22/85 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Notes, Minutes 3/1/85 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Notes: Weissert 3/1/85 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Notes: NYS Validation 3/5/85 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Notes, Minutes 3/13/85 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Notes, Minutes 3/20/85 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Notes, Minutes 4/3/85 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Notes, Minutes 4/10/85 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Notes, Minutes 4/18/85 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Work Plan 4/19/85 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Notes, Minutes 4/26/85 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Notes, Minutes 5/1/85, 5/29/85, 6/17/85, 7/10/85, Phone Call: Judy Powell 4/15/85 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Notes, Minutes 5/7/85 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Notes, Minutes 5/14/85 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Notes, Minutes 5/21/85 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Notes, Minutes 5/28/85 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Notes, Minutes 6/4/85 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Notes, Minutes 6/12/85 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Notes, Minutes 6/18/85 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Notes, Minutes 6/27/85 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Notes, Minutes 7/3/85 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Notes, Minutes 7/10/85 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Notes, Minutes 7/17/85 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Notes, Minutes 7/24/85 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Notes, Minutes 7/31/85 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Notes, Minutes 8/7/85 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Notes, Minutes 8/14/85 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/3/85 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/10/85 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/17/85 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Notes, Minutes 9/24/85 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/8/85 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Panel 10/11/85 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/15/85 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/17/85 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Notes, Minutes 10/29/85 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Notes, Minutes 11/7/85 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Notes, Minutes 11/19/85 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Notes, Minutes 12/13/85 - 2/27/86 (Box 4, Folder 100)
    - Critique of Database Management Structure (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Brant's Letter and Initial Data (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Statistics Charts (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Data Tables (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Data Charts, Tables (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Minutes, Data Charts, Tables (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Charts, Tables, Data (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Data Analysis, Charts (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Data Analysis J,i.757 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Data Analysis (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Data Analysis (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Data Analysis (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Merging of Battelle Databases (Data, Minutes etc.) (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Battelle Database, Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Battelle Codebooks (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Battelle Codebook (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Data (Battelle) (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Battelle/NYS mapping (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Analyses of Combined Battelle Databases (LTCALL, LTCLCG, LTCBASE) (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Analyses of Combined Battelle Databases (Evens, Evens & Odds) (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Analyses of 1974 & 1977 Battelle Databases (prior to combining) (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Outlier Analysis - Battelle Data (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - # People/Change Analysis (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Data Analysis (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Data Analysis (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - NHC Papers (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - NRC File Listings (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - NHC Blank Data Analysis (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - NRC PC Output (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - NRC FAC Data (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - NHC Exponential Smoothing (Holt's Power Curve) (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Exponential Smoothing (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Don's A Analysis (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - NHC Markov Analysis (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Markov Transition Matrix (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Markov Test for Assumptions (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Chi-Square for NHC (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - NHC PDG Definition (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Dynamics of PDG Membership (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - PDG Data, Report (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Sensitivity Analysis - Don's Analysis (Excess Time) (inc/dec Nursetime weight by 30%) (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Objective Data Day Shift Average Time Scattergrams (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Rehabilitation Data (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - HARC/HPSC Codebook (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - HARC/APSC Codes, Records (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - NYS Long Term Care Study (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - NY State Validation (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - NCHSR Validation (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - 1st Quarter Report (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - 2nd Quarter Report (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - 2nd Quarter Report 1/30/85 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - 3rd Quarter Report (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - 4th Quarter Report (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Helen's Presentation for Oct '85 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Study, Report on Resource Utilization Groups (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Conference on the Impact of Reimbursement Policy on the Quality of Care in Nursing Homes (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Study, Report: A Patient Classification Scheme for LTC (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Special Report: Sampling Plan and Procedure (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Final Report: Battelle Employee Costs (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Final Report: Resource Utilization Groups, Related Material (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Final Report: Resource Utilization Groups (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Final Report: Cost Data Reporting System (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Final Report: Cost Data Reporting System (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Final Report: Long Term Care Facilities Study (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Overlook
    - Proposal (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Proposal Literature (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - 1979-80 Information (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - Resumes (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - Agreement (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Project Book 1982 (Box 8, Folder 177)
    - Budget (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Pending (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - Budget Information (Box 8, Folder 180)
    - Completed (Box 8, Folder 181)
    - Statements (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Minutes and Agenda (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Correspondence, Data (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - Crorespondence, Data (Box 8, Folder 185)
    - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 186)
    - Correspondence atf (I) (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Correspondence atf (II) (Box 8, Folder 188)
    - Correspondence 1982 (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - Correspondence 1983 (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - Final Report (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - 1981 HIF Data (SMS) (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - Deliverables (Box 9, Folder 194)
    - 1980 Complete (SMS) Medical/Charge Data (Box 9, Folder 195)
    - Charge Data (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - Data (Box 9, Folder 197)
    - Computer, 587 (Box 9, Folder 198)
    - AUTOGRP Groupings (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Nursing Project
    - Letters of Agreement (Box 9, Folder 200)
    - Continuation Grant 5/85 (Box 9, Folder 201)
    - Nursing Advisory Committee Dec 2, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - Nursing Panel May 19, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 203)
    - Consultant Comments (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - Mental Health DRG's (Box 9, Folder 205)
    - CV's of Nursing Advisory Committee (Box 9, Folder 206)
    - Minutes and Correspondence Aug-Dec 1984 (Box 9, Folder 208)
    - Ninutes and Correspondence Jan-Jun 1985 (Box 9, Folder 209)
    - Data and Correspondence Jul-Aug 1985 (Box 9, Folder 210)
    - Data and Correspondence Sep-Oct 1985 (Box 9, Folder 211)
    - Data and Correspondence Nov-Dec 1985 (Box 9, Folder 212)
    - Minutes and Data Jan-Jun 1986 (Box 9, Folder 213)
    - Minutes and Data Jul-Dec 1986 (Box 9, Folder 214)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Data (I) (Box 10, Folder 215)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Data (II) (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Data (III) (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Hospital and Patient Characteristics 1979-83 Section I (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - St. Lukes, Hospital A (Box 10, Folder 219)
    - Borgess, Hospital B (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - Strong Hospital, Hospital D (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - Hospital E (Box 10, Folder 222)
    - Patterns of Care (Box 10, Folder 223)
    - Pediatrics (Box 10, Folder 224)
    - Data and Minutes (I) (Box 10, Folder 225)
    - Data and Minutes (II) (Box 10, Folder 226)
    - Data and Minutes (III) (Box 10, Folder 227)
    - Nursing Report, Data (Box 10, Folder 228)
    - MA Health Data Consortium: Data, Report (Box 10, Folder 229)
    - Development of a Nursing Cost Allocation Statistic (Box 10, Folder 230)
    - Methodology (Box 10, Folder 231)
    - Categorical Data Analysis Notes (I) (Box 10, Folder 232)
    - Categorical Data Analysis Notes (II) (Box 11, Folder 233)
    - Categorical Data Analysis Notes (III) (Box 11, Folder 234)
    - Fourth Quarter Report 7/31/85 (1st year) (Box 11, Folder 235)
    - First Quarter Report 2nd year (Box 11, Folder 236)
    - Second Quarter Report 2nd year (Box 11, Folder 237)
    - Third Quarter Report 2nd year (Box 11, Folder 238)
    - Final Report Material (Box 11, Folder 239)
  - ICD-9-CM
    - Proposal (Box 11, Folder 240)
    - Financial Material (Box 11, Folder 241)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Literature Reviews (Box 11, Folder 242)
    - Project Minutes 1980-81, codes (Box 11, Folder 243)
    - Project Minutes Dec 1979 - Jan 1980 (Box 11, Folder 244)
    - Project Minutes Sep-Oct 1980 (Box 11, Folder 245)
    - Project Minutes Nov 1980 - Mar 1981 (Box 11, Folder 246)
    - Project Minutes Apr 1981 (Box 11, Folder 247)
    - Project Minutes Apr - May 1981 (Box 11, Folder 248)
    - Project Minutes Feb 1980 - Aug 1981 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Project Minutes Jul 10, 1981 - Aug 31, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 250)
    - New Jersey Physician Comments Summer 1981 MOC 1-12 (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - New Jersey Physician Comments Summer 1981 MOC 13-24 (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Source Material (Box 12, Folder 253)
    - Source Material (Box 12, Folder 254)
    - Development of DRG, 1st Quarterly Report (Box 12, Folder 255)
    - Development of DRG, 2nd Quarterly Report (Box 12, Folder 256)
    - Progress Report (2nd Quarterly Appendices) (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Draft of Assignments to Clinical 'Care Program (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - Assignment of ICD-9-CM (DRG) to Clinical Care Program (Box 12, Folder 259)
    - Classification Scheme Apr 24, 1986, ·Jun 22, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 260)
    - Final Codes (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - Classification Scheme: Definitions Manual (Box 12, Folder 262)
  - Wilson Hospital
    - Organizational Material (I) (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Organizational Material (II) (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - Organizational Charts (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Organizational Charts (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Organizational Charts (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - Ed's Transparencies (Cost, DRG etc.) I (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - Ed's Transparencies (Cost, DRG etc.) II (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Ed's Transparencies (Cost, DRG etc.) III (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Cost Model (I) (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - Cost Model (II) (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Cost Model (III) (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Patient Origin Report 1979 (Box 13, Folder 274)
    - Length of Stay Reports (Box 13, Folder 275)
    - Final Report (I) (Box 13, Folder 276)
    - Final Report (II) (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - Final Report (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - Financial Statements for years ended Dec 31, 1978, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 279)
    - Uniform Financial Report 1977 (Box 13, Folder 280)
    - Financial Report year ended 12/31/78 (Box 14, Folder 281)
    - Computer Print-Outs for Financial Report 1978 (Box 14, Folder 282)
    - New York State Annual Hospital Report (Box 14, Folder 283)
    - New York State Financial Report 1979 (Box 14, Folder 284)
    - Statistics (Box 14, Folder 285)
  - United Health Services
    - Proposal: Ideal-Wilson Medical Center (PRISM) (I) (Box 14, Folder 286)
    - Proposal: Ideal-Wilson Medical Center (PRISM) (II) (Box 14, Folder 287)
    - Care Program Management System Proposal (Box 14, Folder 288)
    - Proposal Correspondence and Related Papers (Box 14, Folder 289)
    - Project Resumes (Box 14, Folder 290)
    - Resumes (Box 14, Folder 291)
    - Application to Hartford Foundation 11/82 (Box 14, Folder 292)
    - Pending 4/83 - 2/84 (Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Agreement I (Research: Fetter) (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Agreement year 2 (Box 14, Folder 295)
    - Agreements (Hospitals) (Box 14, Folder 296)
    - Notes for Presentation (Box 14, Folder 297)
    - 298 Presentation: Handwritten Copy (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Don's Original Proposal for Presentation (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Presentation Originals (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Presentation Transparencies (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Presentation Transparencies (Box 14, Folder 302)
    - Presentation Cost Transparencies (Box 14, Folder 303)
    - Presentation Copies (I) (Box 14, Folder 304)
    - Presentation Copies (II) (Box 14, Folder 305)
    - Actual/Budget Financial Reporting Manual (Box 15, Folder 306)
    - Budget Apr 1983 - Jun 1984 (Box 15, Folder 307)
    - Statements 4/83 - 2/84 (Box 15, Folder 308)
    - Computer 4/83 - 2/84 (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - Completed 4/83 - 2/84 (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - Minutes Apr - Jun 1982 (Box 15, Folder 311)
    - Minutes Jul - Dec 1982 (Box 15, Folder 312)
    - Correspondence 1983 (Box 15, Folder 313)
    - Correspondence 1984 (Box 15, Folder 314)
    - Correspondence year 1 (I) (Box 15, Folder 315)
    - Correspondence year 1 (II) (Box 15, Folder 316)
    - Correspondence year 1 (III) (Box 15, Folder 317)
    - Correspondence year 2 (I) (Box 15, Folder 318)
    - Correspondence year 2 (II) (Box 15, Folder 319)
    - Correspondence year 2 (III) (Box 15, Folder 320)
    - Minutes, correspondence (Box 15, Folder 321)
    - Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 322)
    - Correspondence ye Correspondence, Agreements, Reports (I) (Box 15, Folder 323)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Agreements, Reports (II) (Box 15, Folder 324)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports (Box 15, Folder 325)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Reports (Box 15, Folder 326)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Profiles etc. (Box 15, Folder 327)
    - Yale meeting, 1984 February 7 (Box 15, Folder 328)
    - Training at Yale (Box 16, Folder 329)
    - Research (Box 16, Folder 330)
    - Year 2, Work Sampling (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - Record Formats (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - Physician Reports (Box 16, Folder 333)
    - Activity Reports (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - Physician Lists (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - Patient Log (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - HSMG Time Schedules (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - Dietary and Nursing Weights, LOS Trim Points (Box 16, Folder 338)
    - CT Commission on Hopitals and Health Care: Study on Fixed Variable Costs (Box 16, Folder 339)
    - Cost Model (Box 16, Folder 340)
    - Cost Model (Box 16, Folder 341)
    - Data Catalogs (Box 16, Folder 342)
    - Listing of Revenue OOOes for Ancillary and Nursing (Box 16, Folder 343)
    - Record Layout (Box 16, Folder 344)
    - Long Term Care Databases (Box 16, Folder 345)
    - Fixed Variable Analysis 6/84 (I) (Box 16, Folder 346)
    - Fixed Variable Analysis 6/84 (II) (Box 16, Folder 347)
    - Fixed Variable Analysis 6/84 (III) (Box 16, Folder 348)
    - Fixed Variable Analysis 6/84 (IV) (Box 16, Folder 349)
    - Patient Origin Study (I) (Box 16, Folder 350)
    - Patient Origin Study (II) (Box 16, Folder 351)
    - Patient Origin Study (III) (Box 16, Folder 352)
    - Patient Origin Study 1979 Clinical Care Program Listings of Other Zip Codes (Box 17, Folder 353)
    - Patient Origin Study 1979 Clinical Care Program Listings of Other Zip Codes (Box 17, Folder 354)
    - Patient Origin Study 1980 Clinical Care Program Listings of Other Zip Codes (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - Patient Origin Study 1981 Clinical Care Program Listings of Other Zip Codes (Box 17, Folder 356)
    - Patient Origin Report 1982 1st Fiscal Quarter (Box 17, Folder 357)
    - Patient Origin Reports 1979, 1980, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 358)
    - Patient Origin Study (Box 17, Folder 359)
    - Specifications and Formats for Procedure Files (Box 17, Folder 360)
    - Procedure Profiles (Box 17, Folder 361)
    - Procedure Profile Background Information (Box 17, Folder 362)
    - 5 Month ICR's, Broken Down by Hospital (Box 17, Folder 363)
    - HSMG Progress Reports Jul 1982 (Box 17, Folder 364)
    - Utilization Report (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - AUTOGRP
    - AUTOGRP: An Introduction (Box 17, Folder 366)
    - AUTOGRP: A PSRO User's Guide (Box 17, Folder 367)
    - Reference Manual (Box 17, Folder 368)
    - Command Summary (Box 17, Folder 369)
    - AUTOGRP/SAS Interface (Interactive Mode) (Box 17, Folder 370)
    - AUTOGRP/SAS Interface for Analysis (Box 17, Folder 371)
    - Sample Session (Box 17, Folder 372)
    - AUTOSEL (subfile) (Box 17, Folder 373)
    - Tutorial (Box 17, Folder 374)
    - Training Session Video Tape Outline (tapes 1-11) (Box 17, Folder 375)
    - AUTOGRP: An Interactive Data Retrieval and Descriptive Data Analysis System with Applications to PSRO Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 376)
    - Applicaitons of the AUTOGRP Computer System as a Patient Monitoring Mechanism (Box 17, Folder 377)
    - AUTOGRP Papers, Transparency Negatives (Box 17, Folder 378)
    - Extension of AUTOGRP Capability and its Integration in to the Total PSRO Data and Information System: Final Report (Box 17, Folder 379)
  - St. Vincent's Hospital
    - St. Vincent's Hospital Literature (Box 18, Folder 380)
    - St. Vincent's Hospital: Studies, Correspondence etc. (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - DRG
    - Proposal and Related Material (Box 18, Folder 382)
    - Final Report Vol. I (Box 18, Folder 383)
    - Final Report Vol. II (Box 18, Folder 384)
    - Final Report Vol. III (Box 18, Folder 385)
    - Appendices (Box 18, Folder 386)
    - DRG's and Nursing Resouces (Box 18, Folder 387)
    - The Management and Financing of Hospital Services Dec 1986 (Box 18, Folder 388)
    - The Management and Financing of Hospital Services Feb 1988 (Box 18, Folder 389)
  - Miscellaneous Proposals
    - Geisinger Medical Center Proposal (Box 18, Folder 390)
    - Preliminary Proposal for the Development and Testing of a Case Mix Approach to Hospital Management (Box 18, Folder 391)
    - Health Systmes Research Program: Grant Proposal and Related Materials (Box 18, Folder 392)
    - Advanced Education Program in Health Policy and Health Policy Management, Proposal (Box 18, Folder 393)
  - Miscellaneous Reports and Papers
    - Working Papers (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - Development of an Ambulatory Patient Classification Scheme (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - Conversational Modeling Language (Box 19, Folder 396)
    - Cases in Health Policy Management (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - SOM Case Studies (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - A Case Mix Approach to the Integration of PSRO, Rate Setting and Planning Functions for Acute Care Hospitals (Box 19, Folder 399)
    - Implementation, Evaluation and Extension of a Patient Care Monitoring Mechanism Jun 27 1975 - Oct 31, 1977 Final Report (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Development, Testing and Evaluation of a Prospective Case Payment Reimbursement System: Progress Report May 1978 (Box 19, Folder 401)